The game is afoot.
Sherlock Holmes: A Game of Shadows is a adventure,
action, crime film directed by Guy Ritchie.
There is a new criminal mastermind at large (Professor Moriarty) and not only is he Holmes’ intellectual equal,
but his capacity for evil and lack of conscience may give him an advantage over the  detective.
Sherlock Holmes, played by Robert Downey Jr..
Dr. John Watson, played by Jude Law.
Madam Simza Heron, played by Noomi Rapace.
Professor James Moriarty, played by Jared Harris.
Irene Adler, played by Rachel McAdams.
Inspector Lestrade, played by Eddie Marsan.
Sherlock Holmes: A Game of Shadows is a 2011 period mystery action
film and a sequel to the 2009 film Sherlock Holmes.
The film is directed by Guy Ritchie and produced by Dan Lin,
Joel Silver, Lionel Wigram, and Susan Downey.
The film's screenplay was written by Kieran Mulroney and Michele Mulroney.
Robert Downey Jr.
and Jude Law reprise their roles as Sherlock Holmes and Dr.
John Watson, respectively, alongside Noomi Rapace as Madame Simza "Sim" Heron, Jared Harris as Professor Moriarty, Stephen Fry as Mycroft Holmes,
Kelly Reilly as Mary Morstan, Eddie Marsan as Inspector Lestrade, William Houston as Constable Clark, and Rachel McAdams as Irene Adler.
Although the film follows an original premise, it incorporates more closely elements of Conan Doyle's
short stories, including "The Final Problem" and "The Adventure of the Empty House".
In the film, Holmes and Watson travel across Europe with a Romani fortune-teller to foil an
intricate plot by the cunning Professor Moriarty to instigate a major European conflict.
Though the film received predominantly mixed reviews from critics, with praise for the action sequences and the performances of Downey, Law, and Harris, and
criticism over the poor use of its supporting cast, particularly McAdams, it was commercially successful, with a worldwide gross of over $543 million.
A third film to be directed by Dexter Fletcher is currently in development hell.
The film explores themes of london, england, paris,
france, detective inspector, steampunk, buddy.
The tone is thought_provoking and mind_bending.